moosejaw.com 2019-12-08

# Moosejaw Privacy Policy at Moosejaw.com

Amended: October 2019

New Moosejaw, LLC ("Moosejaw") is committed to protecting online user privacy because we love you. In order to help ensure your privacy, information Moosejaw collects through the Moosejaw website at www.moosejaw.com ("Site") is used and disclosed only in the manners and for the purposes described in this Moosejaw.com Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy"). Moosejaw is a part of the Walmart family of companies.

**Information Collected from Users**  
You share Information with us in various ways. For example: 

• When you email us, ask a question or comment to Moosejaw or submit a customer review;  
• When you create an account or make a wish list, information such as name, email, postal address, telephone number, and gender;  
• When you make a purchase, billing and shipping addresses, including relevant e-mail, phone and credit card numbers and expiration dates  
• When you enter any Moosejaw contests or other promotional features available on the Site. 

**Cookies**  
The Site uses a feature of Internet Web browsers called a "cookie", which is a file that a User's Web browser places on a User's computer's hard drive, to assign an identification code to the computer and to collect browsing information. Cookies may collect information about the type of mobile device you use, your device operating system and browser type, a unique device identifier, the address of a referring websites, the path you take through our websites, and other information about your session on our websites. On this Site, cookies are used in conjunction with session variables to track a User's shopping cart and expire as soon as an order is completed or if a shopping cart sits idle for a lengthy period without being checked-out. Cookies may be used by us or others to collect information about online activities across sites and over time. 

You may set your Internet Web browser to notify you when you receive a cookie or to prevent cookies from being sent. If you prevent a cookie from being sent, you may limit the functionality Moosejaw can provide you when you visit the Site, especially when purchasing an item on the Site. 

**"Do Not Track" Requests**  
Do Not Track is a voluntary program among Internet advertisers that is intended to give users the ability to opt out of behavioral targeting and advertising. At this time, we do not respond to "do not track" settings from browsers.

**Use of Information**  
Moosejaw uses the information collected from its Users to:  
• To fulfill your requests for products and services and communicate with you about those requests;  
• To register and service your account;  
• To administer contests, sweepstakes, promotions, and surveys;  
• To provide customer service and alert you to product information, including recalls;  
• To help us personalize our service offerings, website, and advertising;  
• To help us improve your experience through our website;  
• To send you information about our products, services, and promotions;  
• To respond to reviews, comments, or other feedback you provide us; and  
• To protect the security and integrity of our website and our business. 

**Updating User Information**  
You may review your account information and update or correct any errors. You can also make choices about whether to receive special offers from Moosejaw. To update your account information, go to [Moosejaw.com](https://www.moosejaw.com/), sign into your account, and edit your profile. If you would like to be removed from mailing lists or other promotional emails you can unsubscribe using the "Unsubscribe" link at the bottom of any promotional email. You can also email us at [privacy@moosejaw.com](mailto:privacy@moosejaw.com) and we will take care of your request for you.

**Disclosure of Information to Third Parties**  
Moosejaw may share Information as described below or with your consent. 

We will share Information with our corporate affiliates, including Walmart and Jet. 

We share Information with service providers that help with our business activities, including shipping vendors, billing and refund vendors, payment card processors, and companies that help us improve our products and services. 

Moosejaw may disclose Information about our Users to others if we have a good faith belief that we are required to do so by law or legal process, to respond to claims, or to protect the rights, property or safety of Moosejaw or others. Moosejaw may disclose Information to a third party in the event that another company acquires Moosejaw or part of its assets, or in the event of reorganization, bankruptcy, dissolution, or liquidation of our company. 

From time to time, Moosejaw may share your Information with other companies in order to provide you with a special offer or promotion that we think you will find valuable. Unless you specifically tell us that you do not want to receive these special offers (we can't imagine why), we may share your Information.

**Option to Limit Sharing with Third Parties**  
We only share your Information with reputable companies who provide products or services that we believe interest our customers. Because we love you, and respect you, all Users can opt out of this sharing. If you do not want your Information shared with third parties outside our corporate family for their direct marketing purposes, send an e-mail to [privacy@moosejaw.com](mailto:privacy@moosejaw.com) or call Moosejaw at 877.666.7352. 

**California Privacy Rights**  
Our California customers have a legal right to inquire about the categories of personal information we share with third parties for their marketing purposes. We share personal information with our corporate affiliates, including Walmart and Jet. California customers may send those inquiries to us by email at [privacy@moosejaw.com ](mailto:privacy@moosejaw.com)to learn the categories of personal information that we may have shared during the prior calendar year.

**Nevada Privacy Rights**  
If you are a Nevada resident, you can make a request to Moosejaw to stop the current or future sale of certain types of personal information. To initiate, please contact us at [Nevada.Privacy@Moosejaw.com](mailto:nevada.privacy@moosejaw.com) and provide the following information: First name, last name, email and address.

**Linked Internet Websites**  
The Site may provide links to a third party website not controlled by Moosejaw. These hyperlinked third party websites may collect and disclose Information different than this Site. Moosejaw is not responsible for the collection, use, or disclosure of information collected through other websites, and Moosejaw expressly disclaims any and all liability related to such collection, use, or disclosure..

**Children**  
The [Moosejaw.com](https://www.moosejaw.com/moosejaw/shop/home____) Site is not directed towards children under 13 years of age and Moosejaw does not knowingly collect any information from children under 13 years of age through the Site. Please contact us at [privacy@moosejaw.com](mailto:privacy@moosejaw.com) if you believe we may have collected information from your child through our website and we will work to delete it.

**Security**  
Because we love you, this Site has security measures designed to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the Information under our control, including credit card information that is submitted to Moosejaw. Here are some examples of security measures we use to protect Information: 

• Passwords are required to access your online account and help to protect your account information. Please keep this password confidential.  
• Encryption technology, called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), helps to protect Information in certain areas of our websites during transport across the Internet. The presence of SSL encryption may be indicated by https in the browser URL or the image of a closed lock or solid key in the browser window. These indications may not be present in mobile services that use SSL.  
• For payment card information, we use secured networks, encryption or other protection of cardholder data, physical and technical access controls, monitoring and tests of security systems, and other information security practices to help to protect Information.

**Applicable Law/International Issues**  
We may transfer Information to any jurisdiction where we do business. Even if those jurisdictions do not have the same privacy laws as the jurisdiction where you reside, we will treat Information as subject to the protections described in this Privacy Policy. By providing us with your Information, you acknowledge that you have read this Privacy Policy, understand it, agree to its terms and consent to the transfer of such Information outside your resident jurisdiction. If you do not consent to the terms of this Policy, please do not use this Site. If you have any questions or concerns, please contact us at [privacy@moosejaw.com.](mailto:privacy@moosejaw.com)

**Moosejaw Rewards**  
_Opting-in to Moosejaw Rewards:_  
All users must accept these terms and conditions and create an account with Moosejaw to opt-in to the program and earn, accrue and redeem Moosejaw Reward Dollars (MJ$). The program is FREE to join and membership is ongoing until or unless the user requests to be removed or is removed due to abuse of the program. Users can opt-in to the program while checking out on Moosejaw.com or at one of our stores or at any time within 30 days of purchase to accrue the MJ$ earned on that purchase. Once opted-in to the program, all future MJ$ will earn and accrue for redemption as described below until the MJ$ expire or the user leaves the program. 

All information collected and used to facilitate the Moosejaw Rewards program is directly related to the program's ability to provide value to the customer. A customer opting-in to the Moosejaw Rewards program is a separate action from establishing a user profile as a result of making a purchase. 

The program opt-in requirement was added on August 6th, 2019. Existing program members prior to that date must still formally opt-in and accept the terms and conditions to continue to retain, earn and redeem MJ$. Pre-existing program members that fail to opt-in prior to June 28, 2020 will be removed from the program, and any unused MJ$ will be voided. We really, really don't want to that to happen, so please opt-in or we'll feel terrible. 

_Earning MJ$:_  
All items we sell are eligible with the exception of gift cards or other items specifically noted. Full-priced items earn 10% back while discounted items earn 2.5%. "Discounted items" includes items on sale or discounted via coupon code or use of MJ$. You do not earn MJ$ for shipping or tax charges, only from the item value. MJ$ expire two years after earning and are redeemed on a first-in, first out basis (in other words, we always use your oldest MJ$ that are closest to expiration). 

_Checking & Redeeming MJ$:_  
On Moosejaw.com, just sign-in on any page to see your available balance. Once signed in, you will see your available MJ$ and maximum that can be redeemed in the payment section of the checkout process. In stores, provide the email address attached to your account to learn your balance and apply to your purchase. We will also send you a monthly email that details your balance and other account activity. This is a transactional email that you will receive even if you are not subscribed to our marketing emails. 

_Bonus Rewards Promotions:_  
Every so often, we'll have special offers where you can earn bonus MJ$, like an additional 10%, 20% or 40% back. So if we are running a 50% back special offer, and you buy a regular-priced item for $100.00, you will receive MJ$10.00 in base points, and a bonus of MJ$40. These special offers may have a cap on how many bonus MJ$ you earn during the promotion, but you will always earn the base Reward Dollars. Make sure to check us out on our social channels for other ways to win some extra MJ$! 

_MJ$ on Gift Cards:_  
You don't get earn MJ$ when you buy a gift card, but you do get MJ$ when you spend a gift card. Sorry gift givers. You're welcome gift receivers. 

_Product Returns and MJ$:_  
If you return an item, we deduct the MJ$ earned on that item from your balance. If you used the MJ$ and your balance is less than deduction, then your refund is reduced by the difference. 

_Program Abuse:_  
The intent of the program is to provide our loyal customers with a way to buy great gear for less. Moosejaw reserves the right to remove any user from the program and zero out their MJ$ balance if Moosejaw determines that the user is abusing the program by buying for resale, attempting to game the program or any other reason at Moosejaw's sole discretion.

**Amendments to Privacy Policy**  
Moosejaw reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy periodically. We will post the date this Privacy Policy was last updated. You should check the Site periodically to review the most recent Privacy Policy.

**Contact Information**  
If you have any questions about our services or Privacy Policy, please contact: 

Moosejaw Customer Service  
PO Box 71460  
Madison Heights, MI 48071  
877.666.7352

Love the Madness,  
Moosejaw
